2026-03-17 12:36:31 - STARTING AUTOMATION CYCLE
2026-03-17 12:36:31 - Running Scraper for: Agencia de Marketing Digital Buenos Aires
2026-03-17 12:37:39 - SUCCESS: Finished Agencia de Marketing Digital Buenos Aires
2026-03-17 12:37:39 - Running Scraper for: Agencia de Lead Generation Madrid
2026-03-17 12:38:49 - SUCCESS: Finished Agencia de Lead Generation Madrid
2026-03-17 12:38:49 - Running Scraper for: Consulora Ventas B2B Mexico
2026-03-17 12:39:46 - SUCCESS: Finished Consulora Ventas B2B Mexico
2026-03-17 12:39:46 - CYCLE COMPLETED - Waiting for next scheduled run.
2026-03-17 12:41:35 - STARTING AUTOMATION CYCLE
2026-03-17 12:41:35 - Running Scraper for: Agencia de Marketing Digital Buenos Aires
2026-03-17 12:42:39 - SUCCESS: Finished Agencia de Marketing Digital Buenos Aires
2026-03-17 12:42:39 - Running Scraper for: Agencia de Lead Generation Madrid
2026-03-17 12:43:40 - SUCCESS: Finished Agencia de Lead Generation Madrid
2026-03-17 12:43:40 - Running Scraper for: Consulora Ventas B2B Mexico
2026-03-17 12:44:46 - SUCCESS: Finished Consulora Ventas B2B Mexico
2026-03-17 12:44:46 - CYCLE COMPLETED - Waiting for next scheduled run.
2026-03-17 16:28:59 - STARTING AUTOMATION CYCLE
2026-03-17 16:28:59 - Running Scraper for: Inmobiliarias en San Luis Argentina
2026-03-17 16:29:56 - SUCCESS: Finished Inmobiliarias en San Luis Argentina
2026-03-17 16:29:56 - Running Scraper for: Centros medicos San Luis Argentina
2026-03-17 16:30:51 - SUCCESS: Finished Centros medicos San Luis Argentina
2026-03-17 16:30:51 - Running Scraper for: Estudios contables San Luis
2026-03-17 16:31:45 - SUCCESS: Finished Estudios contables San Luis
2026-03-17 16:31:45 - Running Scraper for: Concesionarias de autos San Luis
2026-03-17 16:32:32 - SUCCESS: Finished Concesionarias de autos San Luis
2026-03-17 16:32:32 - Running Scraper for: Restaurantes delivery San Luis
2026-03-17 16:33:18 - SUCCESS: Finished Restaurantes delivery San Luis
2026-03-17 16:33:18 - CYCLE COMPLETED - Waiting for next scheduled run.
